<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shin Kasbe</title>
    <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shin Kasbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://santiagomunoz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Energy is the currency of the universe</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/energy-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/energy-currency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our currencies used to be backed up by gold, a finite (and scarce)&#xA;resource. Because the supply of gold would not fluctuate much over&#xA;time, this meant that one could move value across time with &lt;em&gt;relative&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;ease. What a nice property, right? What if we could think those terms&#xA;again?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI will teach us to be better humans</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/ai-makes-better-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/ai-makes-better-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Until recently I worked with a particularly difficult TL. He fitted&#xA;the sterotype of Silicon Valley psychopath that sees the people around&#xA;them as disposeable tools to achieve his goals. This person was (and&#xA;is) very smart, and was one of the early adopters of AI in my&#xA;environment. Eventually that got him an internal transfer to another&#xA;more AI-centric position so he moved on&amp;hellip; and came back changed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I structure my learning</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/learning-and-cycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/learning-and-cycles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first months after you start exercising you improve regardless of how&#xA;efficiently you train, just because doing &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; is better than&#xA;doing &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt;. These are called &lt;strong&gt;newbie gains&lt;/strong&gt; and they are everywhere:&#xA;we are bound to make rapid progres at pretty much almost anything that&#xA;we start learning deliberately, at least in the beginning. But what&#xA;happens after the newbie gains are over? You need a method. And if you&#xA;are an adult leading a busy life and wanting to dig deep into a new&#xA;pursuit, that method better be good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second post</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/blog/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/blog/second-post/</guid>
      <description>This is another post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Santiago Munoz, also known as Shin Kasbe on the internet. I graduated from uni as an Industrial Engineer (Electrical Engineer) and dedicate myself to making software and art. In my spare time I also enjoy skateboarding and tinkering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitename</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/content/</guid>
      <description>Pages About My name is Santiago Munoz, also known as Shin Kasbe on the internet. I graduated from uni as an Industrial Engineer (Electrical Engineer) and dedicate myself to making software and art. In my spare time I also enjoy skateboarding and tinkering.&#xA;Posts Energy is the currency of the universe Our currencies used to be backed up by gold, a finite (and scarce) resource. Because the supply of gold would not fluctuate much over time, this meant that one could move value across time with relative ease.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
