<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thinking on Shin Kasbe</title>
    <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/tags/thinking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thinking on Shin Kasbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://santiagomunoz.github.io/tags/thinking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Your coworkers are (probably) not idiots</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/are-you-the-idiot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/are-you-the-idiot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most common water cooler conversations I overhear at the&#xA;workplace is a variation of labeling someone as an idiot. Idiots from&#xA;the past or the present, sometimes even the idiots to come! This&#xA;puzzles me, because the majority of people I have worked with&#xA;have been at least competent. So where are all the idiots I keep hearing about?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy is the currency of the universe</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/energy-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/energy-currency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our currencies used to be backed up by gold, a finite (and scarce)&#xA;resource. Because the supply of gold would not fluctuate much over&#xA;time, this meant that one could move value across time with &lt;em&gt;relative&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;ease. What a nice property, right? What if we could think those terms&#xA;again?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI will teach us to be better humans</title>
      <link>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/ai-makes-better-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://santiagomunoz.github.io/posts/ai-makes-better-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Until recently I worked with a particularly difficult TL. He fitted&#xA;the sterotype of Silicon Valley psychopath that sees the people around&#xA;them as disposeable tools to achieve his goals. This person was (and&#xA;is) very smart, and was one of the early adopters of AI in my&#xA;environment. Eventually that got him an internal transfer to another&#xA;more AI-centric position so he moved on&amp;hellip; and came back changed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
